freelotto.com 2019-11-15

# Privacy Policy

**Collection and Data Utilization Agreement**  
**Privacy Policy/Terms of Use Agreement**  
IMPORTANT: The policies below are applicable to FreeLotto® and other sites owned and operated by PlasmaNet Intl Limited. 

PlasmaNet Intl Limited. collects personally identifiable information during sweepstakes registration and this information is used from time to time as you use our website to: pay prize winnings, confirm entries, and selectively show you relevant ads and/or promotions. We may share your registration information with third parties who may contact you by postal mail with relevant offers; you may unsubscribe to our postal mailing list at any time by visiting your Subscription Preferences through My Account > Player Profile (upper right corner of the FreeLotto website). If you choose to join any of our marketing partners offers, you will be subject to their privacy policy and terms directly.  Your personal information may be shared if required to be disclosed pursuant to an order or warrant issued by a court of competent jurisdiction.

Players' e-mail addresses and other personal information are kept in secure databases to protect our players' privacy. 

_No information should be submitted to or posted at any PlasmaNet Intl Limited websites by guests under 18 years of age. People under 18 years of age are not allowed to participate in FreeLotto® or other sweepstakes offered by PlasmaNet Intl Limited. If such a person wins, his or her entry is void._

All registrants receive e-mail confirming their registration and subsequent entries in FreeLotto® and daily FreeLotto® results with information of interest from FreeLotto®. Additionally, from time to time you may receive other sponsored advertising messages from FreeLotto®. 

You may at any time modify your registration with PlasmaNet Intl Limited by editing your profile on our site. 

Each email we send you will include a description of the simple unsubscribe process to enable you to stop receiving future e-mail of that type from FreeLotto®. You may unsubscribe from each email type this way. For example, unsubscribing from a daily FreeLotto® results email will result in you no longer receiving the daily FreeLotto® results by email. You may however continue to receive other types of email which you can unsubscribe from in the same fashion. 

If you wish to stop receiving e-mail results from PlasmaNet Intl Limited and FreeLotto.com, you can quickly and easily unsubscribe yourself. To do so open results e-mail, scroll down to the line that reads: "If you'd prefer not to receive the results by e-mail, please click below to unsubscribe." If you play FreeLotto subsequent to unsubscribing from all e-mails, you are giving PlasmaNet Intl Limited. definite permission to resubscribe you to all mail types and your subscription to receive email results and other promotions will be automatically reinstated. This is necessary because of the substantial amount of money you can win. Your prize notifications are sent via email and it is important to respond to these emails to claim any prizes won. Furthermore, it is the sponsor that makes FreeLotto prizes possible and in order to play our games you must agree to receive our sponsored messages. 

If you wish to no longer receive any email from FreeLotto, you may at any time modify your registration with PlasmaNet Intl Limited by editing your profile on the "My Account > Unsubscribe" page of our website.

**Your Data Protection Rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)**

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. PlasmaNet Intl Limited. aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete or limit the use of your Personal Data. 

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:

  * **The right to access, update or delete the information we have on you.** Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you.
  * **The right of rectification.** You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.
  * **The right to object.** You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.
  * **The right of restriction.** You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.
  * **The right to data portability.** You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.
  * **The right to withdraw consent.** You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where FreeLotto relied on your consent to process your personal information.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests. You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).

If you wish to be informed about what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please visit [www.freelotto.com/gdpr](https://www.freelotto.com/gdpr) to download all your data and or delete your account. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us at [service@freelotto.com](mailto:service@freelotto.com) to assist you.

**About IP Addresses**  
PlasmaNet Intl Limited collects IP addresses along with web stats and traffic sources, which does not personally identify our users, to administer the site, analyze site usage/trends, and report aggregate information to our advertisers. This information is also used in your welcome email to confirm that in fact you have registered for FreeLotto and will be used in the event that you dispute registration. In some cases an IP address is specific to your computer. In other cases an IP address is randomly assigned with a block of IP addresses which are assigned by your ISP (internet service provider) every time you log on. 

An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your ISP server. Web servers - the big computers that "serve" up Web pages - automatically identify your ISP by its IP address. 

When players request pages from PlasmaNet Intl Limited websites, our servers log and record the players' IP addresses. 

**Cookies - The PlasmaNet Intl Limited Online Cookies Policy**  

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and we hold certain information.

What are cookies? Cookies are small pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier for you by saving your registration, passwords, and references while you're on our site. The use of cookies is an industry standard - you'll find them at most major Web sites. 

By "looking" for a cookie our server can determine whether or not you have already registered to play. Cookies help our server to know you are playing, so that you don't need to register each time you play. 

Cookies also help us to serve you better. Through the use of cookies we can better understand what information interests you, providing more of what you like and want from FreeLotto® and our advertisers. 

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

Some examples of how we use cookies: 

  * **Session Cookies.** We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
  * **Preference Cookies.** We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
  * **Security Cookies.** We use Security Cookies for security purposes.
  * **Advertising Cookies.** Advertising Cookies are used to serve you with advertisements that may be relevant to you and your interests.

A cookie lets our computers remember that you've registered, which allows us to speed up your future activities at our sites. Think of it as a membership card. Similarly, the cookie tracks which of our sponsors you've visited so that we can continue to introduce you to new and interesting sponsors. PlasmaNet Intl Limited may use information we collect through cookies for promotional or marketing purposes. Use of cookies to do the record keeping saves you the trouble of entering information over and over again. If you decline cookies, you may have difficulty playing your selections and adversely impact your FreeLotto® experience. We make our cookies available on an anonymous basis to other advertisers and Advertising Networks so that they can serve you ads for products you are interested in. For example, if you expressed interest in buying a new car you may receive ads about cars. However, we DO NOT include personally identifiable information with the cookies. 

**What FreeLotto® cookies don't do:**  
We DO NOT use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally provided by you or provided by your browser in a visit to PlasmaNet Intl Limited's web sites. 

_We do not use cookies to track other sites that you visit on the Internet._

You may get cookies from our advertisers if you visit their websites. PlasmaNet Intl Limited and FreeLotto® do not control these cookies, and these cookies are not subject to the PlasmaNet Intl Limited cookies policy. The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is standard on the Internet. As mentioned above, we share non-personally identifiable information with third party ad serving partners so they may bring you targeted offers. This information can be associated with their cookies but will not include personally identifiable information such as your name or address. You may review our advertisers' privacy policies when visiting their sites. To learn more about third party ad serving and how to opt out from a third party ad server's cookie visit [www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/), [http://youronlinechoices.eu](http://youronlinechoices.eu/), and [http://aboutads.info](http://aboutads.info/).

**Use of Data**  
FreeLotto uses the collected data for various purposes:

  * To provide and maintain our Service
  * To notify you about changes to our Service
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
  * To provide customer support
  * To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service
  * To monitor the usage of our Service
  * To detect, prevent and address technical issues
  * To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information

**Service Providers**  

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), provide the Service on our behalf, perform Service-related services or assist us in analysing how our Service is used. These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. 

**Analytics**  

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyse the use of our Service. 

**Google Analytics**  

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualise and personalise the ads of its own advertising network. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [policies.google.com](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en%22)

**Advertising**  

We may use third-party Service Providers to show advertisements to you to help support and maintain our Service. 

**Google AdSense & DoubleClick Cookie**  

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Service. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our Service or other websites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick Cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the Google Ads Settings web page: [www.google.com/ads/preferences/](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/)

**Pixel Tracking and Remarketing**  
Pixel tracking is a common online adverting tool, involving the implementation of an invisible pixel tag on a webpage you visit, that is used among other things to target and/or remarket ads (through use of anonymous cookies), compile website usage stats, and measure the effectiveness of advertisements. When employed as a targeting or remarketing tool, the information is collected in an anonymous cookie, which is then used by our advertising to display targeted advertisements to select audiences across the web. For example, if you showed interest in FreeLotto by clicking on our ad in a Google search result, you may be served a FreeLotto advertisement when you visit another website later on. This is made possible through the use of cookies; however, the cookies do not collect personally identifiable information such as your name or address. Some of our business partners (e.g. analytics companies) use cookies and tracking pixels on our site. We have no access to or control over our partners' use of these technologies. To opt out of Google’s use of cookies, visit Google’s Ad Settings: [www.google.com/settings/ads](http://www.google.com/settings/ads). 

Google Ads (AdWords) remarketing service is provided by Google Inc. You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customise the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: http://www.google.com/settings/ads Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on - https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout - for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [policies.google.com](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en)

**Payments**  

We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors). We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information. 

The payment processors we work with are: 

Credorax, Inc

Their site can be viewed at [Credorax.com](https://www.credorax.com/)

**Links to Other Sites**  

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.   
We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services. 

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**  

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page. 

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**  
By using any PlasmaNet Intl Limited. owned and operated websites, you are agreeing to these Terms and Conditions, which include the PlasmaNet Intl Limited Privacy Policy, Official Rules of FreeLotto and the Terms of Use. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our websites. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page frequently for changes. Your continued use of the PlasmaNet Intl Limited sites or your continued acceptance of our results e-mail following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. 

You have the right to revoke the permission you have granted to us to contact you by email as explained above.

PlasmaNet Intl Limited respects your privacy. If you have any questions about this policy please contact us:   
By email: [service@freelotto.com](mailto:service@freelotto.com)  
By visiting this page on our website: [www.freelotto.com/contact](https://www.freelotto.com/contact)  
By phone number: 1 (212) 931-6760  
By mail: PO Box 4562, Grand Central Station, New York, NY 10163, USA
